now we're live again cool yeah I don't
understand this is no maybe the iPhone
was just being weird um let's hope this
is better let me set a topic here
broadcast details not that
[Music]
yeah I know this is hard
um maybe can I change what we're live
about nope I guess I can't okay cool um
so this will be a good rotate there we
go is the stuff fixed do we have a good
orientation now is the stream good
periscope is a lot of problems yeah so
yeah this will be a good stream to watch
if you're interested in porting to your
own car so what we're about to do is tap
into the existing system on this car to
see how that system is commanding the
brake gas and steering what happened I
press the whole bottom iPhone it's kind
of annoying we should get a get a better
streaming setup yeah but this is good
quality good bad reception yeah it's
good cool so yeah what you're gonna want
to do is you're gonna want to sniff the
can of buses right at the camera so this
car has a has a camera just like the
Honda and it has two can buses on it one
that looks like it goes mostly to the
radar and the other one that talks to
this driving support module so I haven't
seen a driving support module before it
may actually be doing some of the math
of steering the car so in which case we
might have to replace that as well but
for now we're just gonna be focusing on
yeah you have to find the canvas wires
after the firewall um so a lot of cars
have these Gateway units in them now and
the Gateway unit is block certain cam
messages though I believe that if we
download the manufacturer Diagnostics
tools we'll be able to send special
messages to the Gateway to bypass the
gateways at least bypass them for a read
only and there's no security issue with
read-only so I would guess that there's
some way to enable that kind of
messaging and that's something we're
definitely going to start looking into
with the Panda project and the chipper
you know because obviously with the
Panda we want to gather you know data
from all the sensors of your car and
well yeah we get to that we'll get to
that much much later maybe next week bye
so we're setting up a wire right now and
this wire is going to use the Ethernet
jack on the giant panda board here no we
don't talk to OEM is talking to OEMs is
hopeless we would be happy to start to
talk to smaller Chinese OEMs once we
really believe that they are going to
build a car
some of them like you know Faraday
future maybe will never actually ship
that car as much as they might want to
but yeah so that's the Ethernet ports on
the neo heat shrink over there yes farad
Faraday is kind of out of money and
that's kind of the problem
you treating the labels we did a label
on this knee oh by the way the serial
number maybe we should write that as a
three-team you as well you know what
I'll make the label is a label maker
label makers cool so that's the serial
number there of our neo and then you can
see that this is running open pilot zero
point three point four not released yet
zero point three point three is
available in the development branch so
let's go here let's type this in 7-6 8-6
to a six use a capital A seven six eight
six to F a six that's right you know I
wish that my phone was also a tiny drone
so I could let go of it and then it
would stay still or a tiny drunk drunk
yeah right because now I have to somehow
put this label on this thing his lucid
motors still a thing I don't know I
think so yeah maybe yeah I need someone
to hold the camera I've run into this
problem on mpz as well you know what
we'll hold the camera right now
get viv viv doesn't want to be on
periscope okay oh well there's 44 people
watching because I messed the periscope
up this is them are we 47 they say
they're happy to see you hold this
camera while I apply labeled in the
other it faces the other way I think oh
my god
someone had this map when they were a
child nice jacket thank you Peter I
appreciate that the periscope lesson
during math yeah it's a good map we got
a target what happened to George's hair
he got it cut I'm putting a label on it
you know it's not it's not the highest
tech okay but yeah so you see this has
the GoPro mount on it um so this is 3
times VHB tape where fans of VHB tape so
this will slide on and off just like a
GoPro slide this off slide this on and
you get similar rigidity that you do
with the rear view mirror I'm also for
phones you logitech notes
pretty great George said you're taller
than they expected not that tall Yeah
right
don't kid yourself hey boss I got
Photoshop for all these things today
mate oh cool
Scott wolf welcome it's their first and
periscope it's the first day I've heard
we actually should welcome more resin
the more rigid oh god they're asking for
this fits better those suction cup now
it is better than a suction cup now so
actually the lack of rigidity of this
suction cup mount
doesn't come from the suction cup it
comes from this attachment point here
like there's a bit of wobble remember a
phone is a pretty long lever arm right
so there's a bit of wobble in this mount
I really wish some company
just make a phenomenal suction come out
I'm because it's not really the fall to
suction cup but um the nice thing about
this VHB mount as well is it gives you
some repeatability of installation
all right so Neos right now still take a
long time to calibrate if you want to be
able to take it out of your car put it
back in your car we know 61 wow they're
coming back San Juan or are there going
to be a solution to the recalibrating
yes there is yes we don't we have we
have a person working on this right now
it involves a fancy machine learning oh
yeah obviously no it does actually the
current calibrator does not use fancy
machine learning but on the new
caliphate early dance machine learning
cool cable over here yeah this is what
separates the amateurs from the
professionals is heat shrink and label
guide okay it's secret
then max
so why sublime text between us I like
sublime text and then these pins gonna
like go in there nicely another nice and
long there long bring let's bring the
diamond cutters with us okay well
Matthew slant progress uh it's going
well we have two full-time people on it
so yeah they'll be somewhat incredible
announcement supposed to get some semia
viewers that's right
seventy-eight viewers we're almost at
100 you guys know what happens at 100
we're revealing a new car oh that's
what's happening because you know oh oh
the place yeah yeah did they post I
don't think if that's public there yeah
what did they post I don't know they
just said someone knows yeah yeah oh is
our occasions on there these cherry gave
me up against you they're saying that
they should have convinced me to tell no
secrets
yeah but randos are a shot on sight
you think I'm kidding
tell that to the three rainbows buried
in the backyard
what the randos been shot that you
aren't being such a mess to cover it up
what yeah look at the poorgrass oh you
might find some Pokemon in the tall
grass so you might find some Bob that's
our new table for you guys to know that
is our check outside yeah but it's okay
Wow okay should I just continue funny
just recording I explain what you're
working on people are people are just
labeling this cable that's going to
connect to the NIA that George is going
to use to plug yeah well I think no I
think we might have the secret location
Jesus um well that's that's that's not
idea that's disabled that just go to
location services yeah oh well you know
hey can't stay secret forever yeah we're
no longer self um well we're right now
someone's messed up something but you
know justjust in case some crazy live
streaming is is stealth mode in case
Hue's can you guys tell this is the
first time we've done this if the more
you flip the camera it's nauseating
that's my experience okay well this is
the second time okay I'll go get the car
guys get the stuff ready tom is walking
at something really rude comments
commenting on my terrible video oh
really all right you guys are good but
I'm just no it's not go thank you Tom
all right I'm gonna show you guys this
is our plant that has died when are you
coming to hang oh we do have lions yes
yeah there's some k7e I've been trying
to mess we have a nest cam so don't even
think about it I had a deets on you with
the giant panda this gives you two
Ethernet ports we're using one of them
to power the car doesn't have to so
we're gonna use this one here for power
because there's no so here's the camera
over here and if you look on you just
turn power off to the car you look on
this connector here there's actually no
full power on this yeah so there's
there's two cam buses but the power is
gated based on ignition and we want your
neo to be able to continue uploading oh
there's no Sun
knocking on car already no sunroof folks
this is the toyota prius for those who
are wondering yeah to give back to me
okay i'm gonna spin you around slowly
it's not I know I know a Prius of some
sort yeah so it is it is a seventeen
Prius part of the reason we picked it is
it can do full speed cruise control it
also has self-park um so by tapping into
the self-park feature down here we can
actually turn the wheel wall car stopped
so you know hey maybe we're gonna do uh
a little more than highway in this car
maybe headlight system malfunction
contact your dealer called the deal but
Lane Departure alert mouth big deal
dealer Wow cars are broken it's not
ready to drive um what are we gonna do
well I mean if only we had some people
who knew some stuff about cars
okay so let's um man it's annoying to
pull this driveway and pull out of the
driveway all right let's get this neo
mounted up on the windshield we're gonna
go like here with it what do you want to
go with no no it's kind of annoying with
this yeah it's very slanting slanty a
shit um and like that's really
off-center now Wow okay I know a bit
about cars my car press are pretty nice
yeah so all dirty saying take off the
mirror maybe
that's pretty dirty doesn't that's
pretty nice I mean that's what they give
Eddie the phone right you can definitely
say shit alright can even yeah question
we want a female cable to hook in to the
other side of that right to do the gate
wing of the we want a female cable yeah
I mean ideally in the radar sorry the
camera so what we're gonna do is we're
gonna shove these wires on okay so
that's radar H camera H I know that the
H is the pin six so how do I know what's
been six mmm I know it's labeled here so
that's 12 okay so the H is on the bottom
here so that's gonna be the louver they
are you really think these things are
gonna work we just shove them in the
holes like this oh and then you're gonna
plug it back in what's the idea right
was annoying I remember sitting at the
computer while you were like doing it
yeah kind of fell out a lot but these
pins are done maybe we should use an
oscilloscope oh maybe we should we
should get a portable oscilloscope we
should buy one yeah those are those are
cool and then we can like see if we're
making good contact yeah
yeah if anyone I hope there can find
this 12 pin now yeah this 12 pin next
year that's on Toyota's it's also the
same one that's being used on the new
Civic hatchback sport I kind of think
it's the same system no I believe they
switched Toyota and Honda seems like
they can partner it up on this and
what's Bosch it's on the Honda it's a
Bosch system and this is as well right
you see ba they're all using the same
system
Bosch is denser then sir
yeah Denso is kind of Toyota so Honda
uses Nyack and Toyota uses Denzil yeah
we're gonna pull power off the ODB port
this can just go down here in the ODB
port it's a little annoying that we have
to get we're just doing it for power
maybe we should just pull power we could
power the power yeah now so that green
oh really oh no it's good it's good okay
I just need to reflash okay okay now if
we plug this in and we see green we
should be good let's turn the car on
oh these are falling out
this is so janky okay
okay radar can work so we're getting
we're logging the radar can right now
yeah so you see that green light so
there's just a panda in here you know
that pandas with the latest firmware
turned green when you're logging stuff
I'm just gonna unplug that so that stops
logging a picture of my face did you
want to take over yeah it's still it's
still logging so yeah a few things we
got to do we got to shove these wires
and better and you want to get some
electric tape then you want to put them
in Nice well we know one of them so
that's what we got to kind of figure out
where to put this and one of any
suggestions aside from removing so
honestly even if we remove the rear view
mirror this is in the way I'm worried
that the best answer might be here you
know so this has a different angle let's
just fire this up
under the hour right now yeah fired up
we can look at the camera and see what
it's seeing but yeah this this this
windshield did a very different angle
from the Honda like look at how angled
Venice be here maybe actually kind of
above the mirror the mirror down there
and have this up here kind of like it
man you know let's just make sure the
camera doesn't look at this so once
Eddie gets that taped up we'll be able
to fire up open violet and then this
will be logging our first star when you
get out good electric tape gaff tape is
far superior to get electric tape my car
is very angry at me it looks like
by the way here we go Eddie your minutes
of fame these folks have been with us
for 24 minutes how many threads how many
folks the wheel we got 55 they're like
really sad they're tired you know they
stayed around for the big reveal
so these two on the left are the other
two yeah the one on the left yeah but
you can so you know it's the same like
toreador as i put the radar yeah it's on
the right oh it's right next to it's
right next to the right stinks
it's just so hard I know cuz we're
shoving wires into little shits you know
but no literally we didn't test any of
this so we're trying to connect it to
the wire trying to connect it so we're
gonna see what the stop system is
sending to the car in order to trigger
the lane Keith and the adaptive cruise
the limbus is not used on this car no
but um the Accord uses something that
looks very similar to Lin for steering
also the acure uses limb for reflashing
or something like lane you know lane
Kaline any of these sort of one wire
serial protocols can all kind of be done
with the same
I can see for Harbor and the Panda
supports Toulon buses so some people
already in early and earlier Candice
yeah start reversing it makes sense when
shopping for a car to port to what are
the main features needed so um we look
for two features we look for adaptive
cruise control and lane keep assist um
if you want to use open pilot on the
highway you're gonna look for those if
you want to move to you know higher
torque stuff you want to look also for
self Park but mainly the features you
want to look for are adaptive cruise
control and latest green we're good I
actually can't see if we're getting both
I'll go get my laptop yeah you can see
mommy yeah yeah and then we're guessing
well just tape tape it up nice but oh
you want to you want to verify yeah if
you can't really taping it up nice isn't
gonna go that far but yeah check out the
steering wheel optical fiber stuff
a little bit too nerdy for Paris thank
you we take that as a compliment
the steering that looks like a
stormtrooper right it's pretty funny
looking
that's like white plastic I really like
these toggle switches oh okay George
with his laptop
he's been slowly spinning don't be dead
I cool good so the way that we can
access all of our Neil's
if you build a neo this isn't true but
the Neos that we build are all on a VPN
very similar to Tesla's cars so I see a
bunch connected to the VPN right now and
then the serial number on that one
starts with seven six seven sixteen all
right so let me connect up to that neo
um so that neo is running the open pilot
software so I can just team ox attach if
you're familiar with it
and I can go in just something that's
shipped in open pilot self-drive debug
yeah I don't like showing my computer
screen unless I think about it more but
yeah so I'm just gonna dump the can bus
so we're here with Vivian and Eddie so
we're dumping the canned messages as
they appear on the on the thing all
right you plugged in I don't see any
cameras such as Yap you gotta you gotta
hit the power but on the car yeah it's
like that all right we're starting to
see some messages all right let me just
make sure we're getting messages on both
buses and not just one I'm seeing
messages on vehicle can and not seeing
messages on radar can well let me just
do the control see and grap yeah it
should be right next to it so let me
grab source what not sec
I'm still only singing on one bus it is
possible the car is only setting on one
bus put it in full accessory mode so hit
the button again you're in this house
remodel
yep I'm seeing both yeah you got alright
so just just tape it up
this is Annie over here um this is the
raw data from the car yeah we're dumping
has got these nice new scissors guys
that's not on dude that's I'm actually
SSH into the phone running the it's
hurting me OS so it's the same new OS
that we've publicly released
smashing that in hopefully it's still
good
people how safe is reverse-engineering
I mean it's safe it's in read-only mode
right now
so if open pilot doesn't fingerprint
your car as an own car it goes into
read-only mode
um the Prius does have low speed like
the Civic that's one of the reasons we
bought it so it's actually the only
Toyota I believe with full speed dynamic
cruise control so we verified it I mean
that's not going to turn right off
because there's still some canned
messages cool yeah well no tape it up
better that gonna mount this - no no I
want you to tape up those wires so
they're not gonna fall out right don't
worry about that it's gonna go there but
don't worry about that just even just
tape it to the taper to the aftermarket
radar possible yes definitely you can
buy so if you want it to be don't give
it to the mirror on tape it to the wire
right so you have a wire that you're
already with you can unplug that if you
want and then just tape it to the wire
um so all of the cars that have TS s P
we can get just unplug it and like tape
it to the wire oh I'm plugging it unplug
it if it's gonna fall out when you
unplug it unplug it now we want this
thing to be in here for a long time
careful um yeah yeah so we're not TS s P
is Toyota's safety cents P edition as
opposed to see edition which isn't as
good i don't name these things um yeah a
core doesn't have low speed follow TSS -
P you can google it sensor Toyota safety
sense P I don't know what perfection
well maybe yeah what didn't the C stands
for crappy all right cool um where do I
see comma fits within big others like
way mo well my business model is nothing
like huevos way Mo's trying to build and
manage fleets we are trying to build
aftermarket self-drive capability
oh I got nan Toyota cars well Oh No give
me a car tell you what I know about it
this is this is going to be our 2017
flagship car the Toyota Prius yeah you
can get a lot of torque with this car
yeah the Subaru might be a candidate I
see it mentioned a lot so the reason
that we pick Hondas and Toyota's is most
of the 10 most popular cars
our founders enjoy us what's gonna turn
on yeah sure as soon as you get a can
message it's gonna turn on all right you
wanna check to make sure we're still
getting both yes all right so you gonna
turn the car on and I'll come back to my
laptop screen here yep so I still think
see things from 0 and 1 we're good all
right so now now you can tape it
stronger somewhere else okay all right
so just make sure that it doesn't and
then we'll work on mounting the camera
we read out ease they can watch me fail
at crash my new Toyota's mounted up
we'll go for a ride yeah we will take
you just a quick ride and then we can go
back to the computer and look on the
dongle idea of the new neo and then we
can analyze it but I don't think we're
gonna show off how we're gonna analyze
but some of you may already know if you
know well you know it's a secret yeah
how did we increase the torque by six
percent well turns out that the Honda
accepts numbers that are six percent
bigger than the accurate we didn't know
this but a reverse engineer at the
firmware found that and then we upped it
to drive around the hooli campus take
videos of his face good thing we're not
in Europe
Chinese the Chinese don't block it how
beautiful Eddie just did automotive
Tech's we don't do that much with cars
actually we're a software company an AI
company we just rig up our cars once or
twice and then we're good to go
well now the people are showing up 91 92
and I guess they're all excited to go
for a ride in their brand-new Toyota
Prius this is your new car - that's true
this isn't just our new thing George get
power from interior lights that have obd
that's not a bad idea this no they're
saying oh you're putting public lives at
risk for your experiments and
entertainment okay we are about to drive
a car and oh my god log some messages
while I safely drive around the
neighborhood
a neighborhood you guys don't know where
it is yes oh everything everything is in
read-only mode right now you know we
spend a lot of time in read-only mode
and no let me let me take a look I'll
switch you'll like it there
I do well let's let's turn the camera on
and see what we get
there's a pretty good maneuver on our
end George you filmmakers gonna be just
like who's that boy Casey nice stuff
yeah she's nice that you want to watch
this yeah our periscope
I like that personally you like that
[Music]
yeah the camera could see pretty well so
the higher up we are the better it gets
yeah you could go there you want to go
there no then we can't slide it off
what oh we got a slide yeah so he's like
bad bit more like there
if yeah that's okay well yeah I mean I
don't really like that you can't see the
hood and we have the same slide off
problem so we could just go we're gonna
look there you know can you see it
already it's America I can't see
anything
can't see anything okay you're thinking
down there I like that Oh actually this
angle works pretty well in about the
angle before but okay let me try it
money let's see from the driver's seat
I wish it slid off the other way yeah
you know I kind of like it there as well
actually looks nice
it's pretty nice all right well then you
know what maybe we just accept it
doesn't really sleep fits in the table
it doesn't slide off it's fine for now
that's fine
classy mopey all right that good yep
somewhat centered maybe so it's pretty
good so you're allowed to have a five
inch square part of the windshield to
mount on under California state laws
I'll stay I wish we had almost another
detachment get a zone you know all right
cool okay
close up the doors let's go for a ride
I'm gonna stay here all right
wait should I go in the front well we'll
see how seamlessly it switches over yeah
so of course this is not calibrated at
all we don't actually expect it to work
but we do expect the logger to work so
this is gonna log everything while we
drive and I'm gonna take it out and
we're gonna try to trigger mount these
cables we're gonna try to trigger both
adaptive cruise and lane keep assist so
we can analyze the logs later and what
did they ask oh I missed it not ready to
drive why are we not are we ready to
drive we're ready to drive let's go
getting out of this driveway is terrible
26 point turn here we come let's try
this maybe does this maneuver at work
you know what you know what's gonna be
great the day that we have like like
some really fancy optimizer figuring out
how to do this for me yeah we're almost
there which uses you some like a-star
search will the GoPro mount work what
nope I'm out they asking it to go for my
work Oh for what oh that you want to use
the window mount for the phone they
don't like you holding it they're just
asking oh I mean oh oh well this will
this mount over there let me focus on
pulling out
[Music]
we look like we're gonna tear yeah yeah
oh this Toyota's got a tight I love this
car you guys it's Chris amazing his car
is pretty oh that's my seatbelt it's
angry property right now so you don't
I'm putting a lot of trust in this
rearview backup fam'ly I should check my
entire surround us oh that's fine that's
just like it's a point I know don't be
worried that's pretty good now like I
hope we can tap into this the side radar
do you think okay I mean alright this is
annoying quickly don't back up quick I
mean then quickly by avoiding the plan
but okay so notice it's complaining
about you see this suction cup is really
good
[Music]
just not about to hit anything if I am
and there's nothing on this side you're
scared okay why is this thing beeping
like I'm about to let you know burn a
house down or something
is this a truck why is it beeping I
think you're gonna be fine
yeah all right one drive all right cool
Wow a difference if it's Friday or
Thursday Oh
yeah we got congestion I mean oh we're
showing your neighborhood yeah that's
gotta be aggressive no sorry folks sorry
folks so let's head toward the highway
let's hope that we can get everything to
trigger before we actually reach the
highway yeah um gonna whole thing yeah
so yeah the things that we're trying to
do right now this is our how many people
with 65 and we're still on one like LT
you don't touch anything else
Oh doodle Meg's a periscope didn't ever
use ooh so I exited periscope before and
I had a bad I was watching it I had a
bad time all right while we're here I'm
bored let's figure out these things work
you wanna you know what no we can't
leave you people we should finish the
driver the people we could put the emo
music on no we can't leave them so we're
logging all the cam messages through
this camera um hopefully use its own
expressway only beware of stopping or
merging vehicles let's go on a
convenient little display there um so I
found the cruise control stock on this
car left a lot to be desired
I'm always afraid someone's yes I rock
it out of there you know okay cool so
the radar is ready so let's engage
cruise control
it's detecting one-lane I think my
cruise control is engaged in 36 it's the
it's the actually the automotive system
that freaks me out more than mine
because my systems are very predictable
all right it's gonna stop is it going to
stop
radar come on it's not stopping very
uncomfortable like it stopped early and
month but okay so honestly they should
understand this the problem is when
you're hitting the brakes you don't want
to apply more pressure as you stop
because then you're this huge jerk at
the end and you want to minimize jerk so
with the controller an open pilot does
is it applies harder brakes at the
beginning and then smoothly lets off the
brakes that's how humans use the brake
that's not how this ACC system uses the
brake so I press the accelerator pedal
to resume this is a safety feature you
see on a bunch of the cars Tesla doesn't
do it so you can see the other thing as
miscalibrated to that's fine I'm cool so
we got an ACC braking event which is the
first thing we need to get now the next
thing we need to get is a lane departure
warning event so we have to make sure
that there's nobody around us when we do
this and then I'm gonna let so this
thing just not apply continuous torque
to the steering it only applies torque
to the steering wheel above 32 miles an
hour and when it detects them about to
drift out of mine let me adjust my
mirrors here and we have no one to our
right so I'm gonna drift
into the right lane here all right let's
see is it putting work on the wheel
it didn't put any torque on this let's
try it again
here we are in the lane or drift
announce yeah okay put a little bit of
torque in a wheel cool so we don't have
to go to the highway let's spin this
thing around let's take it home and then
we can well we're not gonna show you how
we analyze it because you gotta have
some secrets um but you know secrets
don't stay secret forever maybe I'll
keep your eyes out for an announcement
see that the neo is miscalibrated that
would fix itself if it was getting the
right data from the car
the calibration routine needs both the
steering angle and the speed of the car
the new calibration routine won't need
any of this the new calibration routine
will be in the cloud so soon yeah so we
have a twin car what twin car a Prius
well I think it's an updated Prius look
like the same Prius is obviously it
looks like more time with the sea Toyota
by the way guys shout out to melody
Toyota bought this car great people
yeah they take their time for great
people they take their time but yeah
great people we're offense
unlike that time to try to buy a Tesla
we had a great dealership experience but
then you know we are less pleasant
experience the next day they just wanted
to talk to us they wanted us to come
maybe sign a couple papers every time
I'm not big on that kind of conversation
I think you know we don't we don't we
let anybody buy our products
we don't do anything illegal on the
periscope friend
so Quinn's going outside the lane with
Lane keep assist on open that's allowed
you to grab um that's allowed me to oh
yeah
so we assume that the camera we've
tapped into the camera model we assume
that the camera module sent some signal
to the rest of the car to tell the
steering wheel to turn right so we've
logged that signal we've also logged the
braking event from the ACC and then all
of the data is being logged by open
pilot and this is just normal open pilot
just like how you can download and then
that data is going to be sent up to our
cloud where we'll start reverse
engineering it but you know if you have
if you have the right stuff you can get
access to your data as well like if you
you can go into our driving Explorer if
you have can you can click on the purple
check mark and check it out if you have
a pen Green Green all right let's go oh
this car yeah another turn right isn't
this cars pretty amazing right so let's
see if we can raid our fuse of the stop
car actually I'm sure the radar is
tracking that car up there so let's come
to an uncomfortable ACC stop again if we
see it if we see it
it's doing pretty well okay okay not bad
I feel like it's good as long as it's
only using the regen on this car since
Iver has an electric motor um it's good
with the regen but no one who decides to
apply the brakes it's using like a
really bad linear braking model which is
not how humans use the brakes right you
get a driver is really good they teach
you this like limo driver school you
want to step on the brakes hard and you
want to slowly let off as you come to a
stop because jerk this is cruising
school Church know people who have no
people so fun no so it just kicked me
out because it says there's no preceding
vehicle um the cruise control in this
car for some reason if it loses the lead
car at low speeds it just disengages the
cruise control I don't really like when
cars do this so if you saw it just
kicked us out
hey these cars have creep too they like
they put so creep is when you let off
the brake of a car it creeps forward
right now there's no reason this car
should have clean y-yeah and it's
uncomfortable I think the Tesla actually
lets you turn off creep in the settings
which is cool that's cool so to do that
creep creep is particularly smooth I
would rather that when you don't press
the pedals it doesn't move right like
why the cars have this weird thing when
you're pressing no pedals they move
slowly forward what genius came okay so
there's a reason it was true in old cars
but there's no reason it's true in this
car which shuts off the combustion
engine this is a sketchy turn yeah
let's see who can the blind spot
detectors go off I haven't seen them go
off once yeah like there's a car they
hurt why isn't the blind spot detector
car they disabled or have to go through
the settings I mean I hope this car has
it theoretically so this car has rear
cross-traffic alert as well as some side
radars if the user manuals to be
believed no it's this is a Toyota Prius
2 which I was amazed that it had oh
we're gonna show you guys the South Park
we're gonna log see some real torque we
put on the steering so yeah the camera
doesn't control the South Park the South
Park is done by this other module in the
car that all the ultrasonics go into and
stuff so does a chance we're not gonna
capture that we'll probably have to rig
up the same sort of camera wiring
harness for the electronic power
steering you can see the can going right
so will overshoot by one pull in I will
try it out Gate Park easy mode not
currently available using the bomb in
easy mode all right cool they say turn
the blind spot oh that's your blind no
on the buttons on steering wheel which
buttons
no that's not my blind spot we can try
to turn that on and see if we can
trigger that oh it's turning off easy
mode have to start the thing I like the
mode all right we're gonna we're gonna
go through the very confusing menus to
see if we can get the blind spot now now
pull in here and do the self parking
which is surprisingly good I don't
really have a lot of good things to say
about that's corrective it feels great I
feel good in it it goes as fast as I
press the pedal you know I did yell oh
yeah you still do the paddles yeah it
yelled at me for going too fast
yeah yeah okay you went that right good
all right pressing the P button when
parallel parking go forward space
detective go forward stop the vehicle
shift are applied brake checks around
look at this see now that's putting a
lot of torque on the steering wheel you
know it takes a lot of torque to turn a
wheel when it's stopped
so let's see it's gonna turn back here
this thing is impressive and it's
actually kind of useful but I'm afraid
that I would hit now I hit the kerb
hit the curb okay park this guy what
some suspended steering real time great
working you eyes folks cool time
so we're saying goodbye for now this was
comma shows off our new car and starts
on our Toyota port thanks for watching